Exchange. The major averages
all lower again today, but the
recent tech sell off taking a
bit of a breather despite the
recent rotation out of tech. My
next guest still sees
opportunity there. So joining
me now is Matt Miskin, co-chief
investment strategist at
Manulife John Hancock
Investments. Matt, it's great
to have you on. And let's start
right there. What do you think
of stocks at these levels and
where do you think we go from
here?
>> Yeah, Morgan today is a day
that reminds you that the
market was really looking
forward to some rate cuts and
the thought that the economy is
actually accelerating here into
August, based on the PMI data,
is causing a bit of a sell off.
But in our view, there's value
to be had in some of the names
that are being sold off as high
quality stocks have been the
laggard, we actually think
they're going to be making a
comeback in the back half. We
think they've been
underappreciated in terms of
earnings growth this year. A
lot of capital has chased
momentum stocks. This year we
would move back into quality
use that strong balance sheet
high ROE good profit margins to
get you through this volatility.
>> Where do you see quality.
What will you do. Find US
quality.
>> Yeah. So technology always
has been the poster child I
mean the earnings growth the
balance sheets the profit
margins. It has it all the
valuations are rich. But the
earnings growth is of the best
in the world. And then
communication services similar
story. We also are looking at
industrials. You can find high
quality industrial companies
benefiting from the onshoring
CapEx boom we're seeing across
the country. So those three
sectors are really our
favorites. But what we're
seeing more broadly is a market
that's tapped out in terms of
multiple expansion. And we're
looking for companies that can
deliver earnings growth to us.
And that's going to be the key
driver of returns from here is
really earnings growth.
>> So in light of that us
versus the rest of the world
what do you think.
>> So this is.
>> On tap for one of the best
years in Europe Europe's
history in terms of markets.
It's it's been quite a
counterintuitive year. You
would have thought tariffs
would have caused non-U.S.
markets to struggle. They are
having the best year ever. And
you really want to look at the
fundamentals though. Earnings
growth outside the United
States in terms of the FAA at
least is tracking about 3% this
year. The S&P 500, it's over
10%. We are not seeing this
loss of exceptionalism here in
the United States. The PMI
readings today for August just
showed the US came back
swinging in terms of the soft
patch that had been developing
at the start of the summer. US
earnings power is the best in
the world. Yes, there's a
valuation gap, but the thing is
Europe has rallied all on
multiple expansion, all on
valuation rerating. We think
that's starting to get tapped
out okay.
>> So if I look to tomorrow and
Fed Chair Powell's speech at
Jackson Hole, there had been an
expectation that maybe he'd
he'd tilt a little more dovish.
Now, maybe not so much. What
are you anticipating do you
think September is live for a
rate cut here or could
inflation be stickier?
>> Yeah, we do think September.
>> Is going to be a rate cut
Morgan. But what we're seeing
today was a good microcosm of
the torture that the fed is
going through. So we got
initial jobless claims higher
and continuing claims are at
all time cycle high. Philly fed
missed. And then the
manufacturing PMI and services
PMI boomed. What do you make
out of all that. Hard to say.
It's all over the place. And so
as the fed is trying to
navigate this, it is not giving
them much confidence. Going
into the September meeting. I
think the market's already set
on a September cut, but October
and December are still up for
grabs. And that's why this
market is a little choppy here.
Because if those aren't going
to be cuts, we think that the
market multiple might come down
a bit. You got to hold on the
higher quality earnings. Well
strong earnings companies to
get through that.
>> All right. So what does that
mean for fixed income as well.
Do you see compelling
investments to be made there.
>> Yeah we do.
>> I mean at the end of the day
we have broadly seen
disinflationary forces. Housing
data just came out today.
Inventory is up 15%. We're
seeing nationally housing
prices decline outright. So
declining housing prices. We've
got oil prices that have been
contained. Commodity prices are
down generally speaking. And
then wage growth is slowing
indeed came out with some wage
growth data wage growth slowing.
So we're seeing disinflationary
forces across the board. And
really it's just the tariffs
that are causing inflation. But
all these other things should
be disinflationary enough to
get the fed to be able to cut
more. So in the back half or
into the final quarter here.
That's one thing we think will
end up materializing. But we
are in a tough spot because the
next month it is giving a mixed
emotions or mixed picture. And
we just got to be careful here,
not adding too much risk,
letting the market settle out.
And then we think actually in
the back in the end